Guide to the Social Service Employees Union Records WAG.003
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series IV: Grievances, Arbitrations and Legal Cases (General), 1953-1999
  - Whitehead, Victor et al v. Thomas Roche et al: Legal Documents, Article 78 Proceeding, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 40)
  - Wilder, Shirley et al v. Blanche Bernstein et al: Legal Documents and Related Materials, 1994 (Box 37, Folder 41)
  - Wilder, Shirley et al v. Blanche Bernstein et al: Legal Documents and Related Materials, 1995 (Box 37, Folder 42)
  - Wilder, Shirley et al v. Blanche Bernstein et al: Legal Documents and Related Materials, 1996-1997, 2001 (Box 37, Folder 43)
  - Women in City Government United et al v. the City of New York et al, 1977 (Box 37, Folder 44)
  - Yavner, Gerald M. v. Jules M. Sugarman: legal documents, Order Under Article 78, 1971 (Box 37, Folder 45)
- Series V: Unprocessed Material, 1976-2007
  - State Legislative Agenda - ACS Out of Title Grievances - Health and Safety Materials - Memoranda of Law, 1998-2004 (Box 38)
  - Social Service Resources - Publicity and Press Releases - Diagnostic Center Materials - Correspondences and Memoranda - Payments - Legal Material - Notes, 1976-2006 (Box 39)
  - Legal Transcripts, Undated (Box 40)
  - Faye Moore Office Materials (Legal: Correspondences, Memoranda, Briefs & Published Guidelines & Meeting and Committee Schedules, Materials, and Publications), 1997-2005 (Box 41)
  - Fay Moore's Office Materials (Correspondences, Briefs, Legal Orders & Petitions, Conference Materials, Joel Spivak Mail), 1999-2006 (Box 42)
  - "Black History" Programs, Materials, Publications, Correspondences, Mailings, Notes, and Records, 1998-2007 (Box 43)
  - Faye Moore Office Materials (Department of Sanitation, AFSCME, NYCHA, Archival Press Clippings, Correspondences, Contact Lists, Balance Sheets), 1996-2003 (Box 44)
  - Ben Caldwell drawing of Adam Clayton Powell, 1984 (Box Shared Tamiment 011, Folder 5)
- Series VI: Archived Websites, September 2007-ongoing; 4 websites in 4 archived websites.
  Scope and Content Note
  Founded in 1965, Social Service Employees Union Local 371 is part of District Council 37 of the American Federation of State, County and Municipal Employees AFL-CIO (AFSCME), which represents workers employed by New York City in social service professions. The website contains information on benefits and grievance filing, and their current and past contracts. The production website contains information on events; a photo gallery; forms for grievances, applications, claims, courses, and annuity; benefits services; and information on grievances, legal services, membership, negotiations, political action, and committees. Also includes the website for the Charles Ensley Scholarship Foundation.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
  Accruals
  New site crawls are accrued semiannually.
  Appraisal
  Crawl was limited to domains and subdomains of sseu371.org, charlesensley.sseu371.org, mightyunionproduction.club and mightyunion.org in order to remain within the collection scope and data constraints.